Center for the Study of Drug Development Records UA093
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Center for the Study of Drug Development Records
1986 -- 2001
1984 -- 2017
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Center for the Study of Drug Development
UA093
1.2 Linear Feet 1 box
1 Digital Object(s)
This collection contains the administrative records and publications of the Center for the Study of Drug Development Records, an independent, academic, non-profit research center at Tufts University School of Medicine.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in seven series: Annual reports; Conference proceedings; Course announcements; Reprints and research publications; Promotional materials; Impact and Outlook reports; and R&D Management Reports.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains brochures, forum reports, annual reports, and publications, as well as conference proceedings, course announcements, promotional materials, and a CD-ROM created by the Center for the Study of Drug Development.
Related Materials
UP191, CSDD Newsletter, DCA.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Center for the Study of Drug Development, 2017.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The Center for the Study of Drug Development (CSDD) was founded by Dr. Louis Lasagna (1923-2003) in 1976 in Rochester, New York at the University of Rochester. Dr. Lasagna founded the CSDD to "provide objective analyses and add an academic voice to policy debates in biopharmaceutical innovation." While in Rochester, the CSDD focused on researching the pharmaceutical industry and its regulation by the United States Food and Drug Administration. The first Director of the CSDD, Dr. William Wardell, led one of the earliest studies in the CSDD, which was an assessment of drug availability in the United States compared to the drug availability in the United Kingdom. The CSDD continued to work on several projects in Rochester, New York until 1984, when Dr. Lasagna was hired as the first Dean of the Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences at Tufts University. When Dr. Lasagna moved from the University of Rochester to Tufts University, he brought the CSDD with him, and it was renamed the Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development (TCSDD) in 1988. As part of the Tufts University School of Medicine TCSDD had new opportunities to increase their research activities, focusing on economic, political, scientific, and legal issues impacting the pharmaceutical world.
Since the creation of the Center for the Study of Drug Development in 1976, the Center has done research in several fields surrounding the development of drugs. The TCSDD was the first organization to complete a comprehensive review of the cost of making a new drug and putting it on the market: $54 million in 1979, which had risen to $2.6 billion by 2014. These studies came under fire in 2016, when the TCSDD and their donors were the focus of protests as part of a global action campaign against high pharmaceutical prices led by ACT UP. Protesters demanded to know the names of donors funding the cost evaluation research conducted by Joseph DiMasi, but TSCDD director Kenneth Kaitin confirmed that no direct funding from any pharmaceutical companies was used in the drug development evaluations, and declined to release donor names, as it was against Center policy. The TCSDD continues to work in several fields related to the development of new drugs, including cost evaluation, biotechnology comparison, FDA policy review, drug effectiveness, regulation timeframes, drug withdrawals, and more.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Academic Centers and Institutes; Research and Research Administration
- Annual reports, 1984 -- 1996; UA093.001; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of the annual reports of the Center for the study of Drug Development.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Annual report, 1984 -- 1985; UA093.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1985 -- 1986; UA093.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA093.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA093.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1988 -- 1989; UA093.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1989 -- 1990; UA093.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1990 -- 1991; UA093.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1992 -- 1993; UA093.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Annual report, 1995 -- 1996; UA093.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    20th Anniversary.
- Conference proceedings, 1986 -- 1997; UA093.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of the conference proceedings and summaries of the forums and conferences sponsored by the Center for the study of Drug Development.
  - Who are the "elderly"?, 1986; UA093.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
    Mortimer H. Appley, Ph.D. and Louis Lasagna, M.D., Editors; Report of a conference held June 23, 1986 on the Definition of Aging.
  - Postmarketing Surveillance of Multisource Drugs, 1986; UA093.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
    Louis Lasagna, M.D., Editor; Report of a conference held July 9-10, 1986.
  - Trends in Product Liability Law and No-Fault Compensation for Drug-Induced Injuries, 1989; UA093.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
    Sheila R. Shulman, LLB, MPH and Louis Lasagna, M.D., Editor; Proceedings of an International Symposium Sponsored by the Center for the Study of Drug Development, September 14-16, 1989, Talloires, France.
  - Moving Prescription Drugs to the Over-the-Counter Market, 1994; UA093.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
    Proceedings from a Forum sponsored by the Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development, May 24, 1994.
  - FDA Accelerated Approval: Dealing with Uncertainty, 1994; UA093.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
    Presented by Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development, ML Strategies, Inc., Project inform, and Gay Men's Health Crisis, September 23, 1994.
  - FDA User Fees in an Era of Proposed FDA Reform, 1995; UA093.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
    Sheila R. Shulman, LL.B., MPH and Louis Lasagna, MD, editors; Proceedings from a Forum Sponsored by the Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development, May 18, 1995.
  - Twentieth Anniversary Commemorative Lectures, 1996; UA093.002.001.00016 (Box 1)
    Sheila R. Shulman, LL.B., MPH and Louis Lasagna, MD, editors; May 1, 1996.
  - Communicating complex medical information: Can we do it better?, 1997; UA093.002.001.00017 (Box 1)
    A Forum sponsored by Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development and Emerson-Tufts Program in Health Communication, April 17, 1997.
- Course announcements, 1986 -- 2010; 1986 -- 1992; UA093.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of announcements of postgraduate courses offered by the Center for the Study of Drug Development.
  - Course announcements, 1986 -- 1992; UA093.003.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Course announcements, 2009 -- 2010; UA093.003.001.00019 (Box 1)
- Reprints and research publications, 1984 -- 1991; UA093.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of the reprints and research publications related to the Center for the study of Drug Development.
  - A comparative retrospective analysis of data for short- and long-term animal toxicity studies on 40 pharmaceutical compounds, 1984; UA093.004.001.00020; Walker, S.R.; Schuetz, E.; Schuppan, D.; Gelzer, J. (Box 1)
  - Testing the methods of assessment for adverse drug reactions, 1984; UA093.004.001.00021; Girard, M. (Box 1)
  - Adverse reactions: Some pitfalls and Postulates, 1984; UA093.004.001.00022; Napke, E. (Box 1)
  - The TPA controversy and the drug approval process: The view of the Cardiovascular and Renal Drugs Advisory Committee, 1988; UA093.004.001.00023; Kowey, Peter R. (Box 1)
  - Congress, the FDA, and new drug development: Before and after 1962, 1989; UA093.004.001.00024; Lasagna, Louis (Box 1)
  - The New Drug Approvals of 1987, 1988, and 1989: Trends in Drug Development, 1991; UA093.004.001.00025; Lasagna, Louis; Kaitin, Kenneth I.; DiCerbo, Patricia A. (Box 1)
    The Journal of Clinical Pharmacology, February 1991, Vol 31, No. 2.
  - Development of supplemental indications for already-approved drugs by the United States Pharmaceutical Industry, 1991; UA093.004.001.00026; Lasagna, Louis; DiMasi, Joseph A. (Box 1)
    Journal of Clinical Research and Pharmacoepidemiology 5, 19-33 (1991).
  - New indications for already-approved drugs: An analysis of regulatory review times, 1991; UA093.004.001.00027; Lasagna, Louis; DiMasi, Joseph A.; Kaitin, Kenneth I.; Fernandez-Carol, Cecilia (Box 1)
    Journal of Clinical Pharmacology, March 1991 Vol 31, No 3.
  - Food drug cosmetic law journal, 1991; UA093.004.001.00028 (Box 1)
    January 1991, Volume 46, No. 1.
  - Drug safety research unit PEM News, 1991; UA093.004.001.00029 (Box 1)
    August 1991, No. 7.
  - Cost of innovation in the Pharmaceutical Industry, 1991; UA093.004.001.00030; DiMasi, Joseph A.; Lasagna, Louis; Hansen, Ronald W.; Grabowski, Henry G. (Box 1)
    Journal of Health Economics 10(1991) 107-142. North-Holland.
- Promotional materials, 1998 -- 2010; UA093.005; 1.2 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of materials used to promote the Center for the Study of Drug Development, including a CD-Rom that contains Impact Reports and other publications and bibliographic information.
  - The Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development brochure, 1998; UA093.005.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - The Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development, 2001; UA093.005.001.00032 (Box 1)
    CD
  - Postgraduate Course in Clinical Pharmacology, Drug Development, and Regulation, 2010; UA093.005.001.00051 (Box 1)
- Impact and Outlook Reports, 1999 -- 2017; UA093.006; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series consists of two publications produced by the Center for the Study of Drug Development: "Outlook," and "Impact Report." For earlier newsletters, see UP191, CSDD Newsletter.
  This series is arranged in order of accession.
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2009; UA093.006.001.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    11, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2009; UA093.006.001.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    11, 4
  - Impact Report, September/October, 2009; UA093.006.001.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    11, 5
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2009; UA093.006.001.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    11, 6
  - Outlook, 2010; UA093.006.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2010; UA093.006.001.00038 (Box 1)
    12, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2010; UA093.006.001.00039 (Box 1)
    12, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2010; UA093.006.001.00040 (Box 1)
    12, 4
  - Impact Report, September/October, 2010; UA093.006.001.00041 (Box 1)
    12, 5
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2010; UA093.006.001.00042 (Box 1)
    12, 6
  - Outlook, 2011; UA093.006.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, January/February, 2011; UA093.006.001.00044 (Box 1)
    13, 1
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2011; UA093.006.001.00045 (Box 1)
    13, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2011; UA093.006.001.00046 (Box 1)
    13, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2011; UA093.006.001.00047 (Box 1)
    13, 4
  - Impact Report, September/October, 2011; UA093.006.001.00048 (Box 1)
    13, 5
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2011; UA093.006.001.00049 (Box 1)
    13, 6
  - Outlook, 2012; UA093.006.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, January/February, 2012; UA093.006.001.00052 (Box 1)
    14, 1
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2012; UA093.006.001.00053 (Box 1)
    14, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2012; UA093.006.001.00054 (Box 1)
    14, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2012; UA093.006.001.00055 (Box 1)
    14, 4
  - Impact Report, September/October, 2012; UA093.006.001.00056 (Box 1)
    14, 5
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2012; UA093.006.001.00057 (Box 1)
    14, 6
  - Impact Report, January/February, 2013; UA093.006.001.00058 (Box 1)
    15, 1
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2013; UA093.006.001.00059 (Box 1)
    15, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2013; UA093.006.001.00060 (Box 1)
    15, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2013; UA093.006.001.00061 (Box 1)
    15, 4
  - Outlook, 2013; UA093.006.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, September/October, 2013; UA093.006.001.00063 (Box 1)
    15, 5
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2013; UA093.006.001.00064 (Box 1)
    15, 6
  - Outlook, 2014; UA093.006.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, January/February, 2014; UA093.006.001.00066 (Box 1)
    16, 1
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2014; UA093.006.001.00067 (Box 1)
    16, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2014; UA093.006.001.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    16, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2014; UA093.006.001.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    16, 4
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2014; UA093.006.001.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    16, 6
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2015; UA093.006.001.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    17, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2015; UA093.006.001.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    17, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2015; UA093.006.001.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    17, 4
  - Impact Report, September/October, 2015; UA093.006.001.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    17, 5
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2015; UA093.006.001.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    Volume, Number
    17, 6
  - Impact Report, January/February, 2016; UA093.006.001.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    18, 1
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2016; UA093.006.001.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    18, 2
  - Impact Report, May/June, 2016; UA093.006.001.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    18, 3
  - Impact Report, July/August, 2016; UA093.006.001.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    18, 4
  - Impact Report, November/December, 2016; UA093.006.001.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    18, 6
  - Outlook, 2016; UA093.006.001.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, January/February, 2017; UA093.006.001.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    19, 1
  - Impact Report, March/April, 2017; UA093.006.001.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    19, 2
  - Outlook, 2000; UA093.006.001.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2001; UA093.006.001.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2002; UA093.006.001.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2003; UA093.006.001.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2004; UA093.006.001.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2005; UA093.006.001.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2006; UA093.006.001.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2007; UA093.006.001.00094; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2008; UA093.006.001.00095; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2009; UA093.006.001.00096; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Outlook, 2015; UA093.006.001.00097; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Impact Report, 1999 -- 2002; UA093.006.001.00100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, June 1999; UA093.006.001.00100.000001 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, July 1999; UA093.006.001.00100.000002 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, September 1999; UA093.006.001.00100.000003 (Box 1)
      1
    - Impact Report, November 1999; UA093.006.001.00100.000004 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, January 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000005 (Box 1)
      2
    - Impact Report, March 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000006 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, April 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000007 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, May 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000008 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, June 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000009 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, July/August 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000010 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, October 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000011 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, December 2000; UA093.006.001.00100.000012 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, January/February 2001; UA093.006.001.00100.000013 (Box 1)
      3, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2001; UA093.006.001.00100.000014 (Box 1)
      3, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2001; UA093.006.001.00100.000015 (Box 1)
      3, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2001; UA093.006.001.00100.000016 (Box 1)
      3, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2001; UA093.006.001.00100.000017 (Box 1)
      3, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2001; UA093.006.001.00100.000018 (Box 1)
      3, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2002; UA093.006.001.00100.000019 (Box 1)
      4, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2002; UA093.006.001.00100.000020 (Box 1)
      4, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2002; UA093.006.001.00100.000021 (Box 1)
      4, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2002; UA093.006.001.00100.000022 (Box 1)
      4, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2002; UA093.006.001.00100.000023 (Box 1)
      4, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2002; UA093.006.001.00100.000024 (Box 1)
      4, 6
  - Impact Report, 2003 -- 2006; UA093.006.001.00101 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, January/February 2003; UA093.006.001.00101.000001 (Box 1)
      5, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2003; UA093.006.001.00101.000002 (Box 1)
      5, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2003; UA093.006.001.00101.000003 (Box 1)
      5, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2003; UA093.006.001.00101.000004 (Box 1)
      5, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2003; UA093.006.001.00101.000005 (Box 1)
      5, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2003; UA093.006.001.00101.000006 (Box 1)
      5, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2004; UA093.006.001.00101.000007 (Box 1)
      6, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2004; UA093.006.001.00101.000008 (Box 1)
      6, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2004; UA093.006.001.00101.000009 (Box 1)
      6, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2004; UA093.006.001.00101.000010 (Box 1)
      6, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2004; UA093.006.001.00101.000011 (Box 1)
      6, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2004; UA093.006.001.00101.000012 (Box 1)
      6, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2005; UA093.006.001.00101.000013 (Box 1)
      7, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2005; UA093.006.001.00101.000014 (Box 1)
      7, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2005; UA093.006.001.00101.000015 (Box 1)
      7, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2005; UA093.006.001.00101.000016 (Box 1)
      7, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2005; UA093.006.001.00101.000017 (Box 1)
      7, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2005; UA093.006.001.00101.000018 (Box 1)
      7, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2006; UA093.006.001.00101.000019 (Box 1)
      8, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2006; UA093.006.001.00101.000020 (Box 1)
      8, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2006; UA093.006.001.00101.000021 (Box 1)
      8, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2006; UA093.006.001.00101.000022 (Box 1)
      8, 4
  - Impact Report, 2006 -- 2016; UA093.006.001.00102 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, September/October 2006; UA093.006.001.00102.000001 (Box 1)
      8, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2006; UA093.006.001.00102.000002 (Box 1)
      8, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2007; UA093.006.001.00102.000003 (Box 1)
      9, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2007; UA093.006.001.00102.000004 (Box 1)
      9, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2007; UA093.006.001.00102.000005 (Box 1)
      9, 3
    - Impact Report, July/August 2007; UA093.006.001.00102.000006 (Box 1)
      9, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2007; UA093.006.001.00102.000007 (Box 1)
      9, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2007; UA093.006.001.00102.000008 (Box 1)
      9, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2008; UA093.006.001.00102.000009 (Box 1)
      10, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2008; UA093.006.001.00102.000010 (Box 1)
      10, 2
    - Impact Report, July/August 2008; UA093.006.001.00102.000011 (Box 1)
      10, 4
    - Impact Report, September/October 2008; UA093.006.001.00102.000012 (Box 1)
      10, 5
    - Impact Report, November/December 2008; UA093.006.001.00102.000013 (Box 1)
      10, 6
    - Impact Report, January/February 2009; UA093.006.001.00102.000014 (Box 1)
      11, 1
    - Impact Report, March/April 2009; UA093.006.001.00102.000015 (Box 1)
      11, 2
    - Impact Report, May/June 2009; UA093.006.001.00102.000016 (Box 1)
    - Impact Report, January/February 2010; UA093.006.001.00102.000017 (Box 1)
      12, 1
    - Impact Report, September/October 2014; UA093.006.001.00102.000018 (Box 1)
      16, 5
    - Impact Report, January/February 2015; UA093.006.001.00102.000019 (Box 1)
      17, 1
    - Impact Report, September/October 2016; UA093.006.001.00102.000020 (Box 1)
      18, 5
- R&D Management Report, 2006 -- 2016; UA093.007; 0.3 Linear Feet
  This series consists of the publication R&D Management Report, produced by the Center for the Study of Drug Development. For earlier newsletters, see UP191, CSDD Newsletter.
  - R&D Management Report, January, 2014; UA093.007.001.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - R&D Management Report, April, 2014; UA093.007.001.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - R&D Management Report, January, 2015; UA093.007.001.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - R&D Management Report, October, 2015; UA93.007.001.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
  - R&D Management Report, 2006 -- 2011; UA093.007.001.00098; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2006; UA093.007.001.00098.000001 (Box 1)
      1, 1
    - R&D Management Report, March 2007; UA093.007.001.00098.000002 (Box 1)
      2, 1
    - R&D Management Report, February 2008; UA093.007.001.00098.000003 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, March 2008; UA093.007.001.00098.000004 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, June 2008; UA093.007.001.00098.000005 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, January 2009; UA093.007.001.00098.000006 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2009; UA093.007.001.00098.000007 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, June 2009; UA093.007.001.00098.000008 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, October 2009; UA093.007.001.00098.000009 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, January 2010; UA093.007.001.00098.000010 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2010; UA093.007.001.00098.000011 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, August 2010; UA093.007.001.00098.000012 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, October 2010; UA093.007.001.00098.000013 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, January 2011; UA093.007.001.00098.000014 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2011; UA093.007.001.00098.000015 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, August 2011; UA093.007.001.00098.000016 (Box 1)
      6. 3
    - R&D Management Report, October 2011; UA093.007.001.00098.000017 (Box 1)
  - R&D Management Report, 2012 -- 2016; UA093.007.001.00099; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, January 2012; UA093.007.001.00099.000001 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2012; UA093.007.001.00099.000002 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, August 2012; UA093.007.001.00099.000003 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, October 2012; UA093.007.001.00099.000004 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, January 2013; UA093.007.001.00099.000005 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2013; UA093.007.001.00099.000006 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, August 2013; UA093.007.001.00099.000007 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, October 2013; UA093.007.001.00099.000008 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, October 2014; UA093.007.001.00099.000009 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, January 2015; UA093.007.001.00099.000010 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, April 2015; UA093.007.001.00099.000011 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, August 2015; UA093.007.001.00099.000012 (Box 1)
      10, 3
    - R&D Management Report, January 2016; UA093.007.001.00099.000013 (Box 1)
    - R&D Management Report, October 2016; UA093.007.001.00099.000014 (Box 1)